Guide to the Frank Moore Papers, 1971-2003 MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Artifacts and Objects, 152674
  - Subseries A: Personal Items, 152701
    - X-rays and report. Chest. Mt. Sinai Hospital [additional materials in oversize box] March 1979, 152704 (Box 25, Folder 1079)
    - X-rays. Nasal bones, New York, May 13, 1980 [additional materials in oversize box], 152703 (Box 25, Folder 1080)
    - Wallet including driver's license, membership cards and metrocard, undated; 152702 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_8c7e740beded1d0da5508942b686440d)
  - Subseries B: Art Implements and Artifacts, 152687
    - Item removed to oversize, 204554 (Box 25, Folder 1081)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204555 (Box 25, Folder 1082)
    - Item removed to oversize, 1992; 152700 (Box 25, Folder 1083)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204556 (Box 25, Folder 1084)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204557 (Box 25, Folder 1085)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204558 (Box 25, Folder 1087)
    - Brushes, trowel style painting knife, burnisher made of wood and agate., undated; 152699 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_e27f215bbc9adaec19a30756947e6137)
    - Diamond shapes, cut out of envelopes, undated; 152698 (Box 25, Folder 1088)
    - DNA transparency, 2000; 152697 (Box 25, Folder 1089)
    - Dress sketches. Found in A History of Costume, undated; 152696 (Box 25, Folder 1090)
    - Enlargement of torture graphic, undated; 152695 (Box 25, Folder 1091)
    - HIV illustrations, ink-jet prints and acetates, undated; 152694 (Box 25, Folder 1092)
    - Lettering examples, undated; 152693 (Box 25, Folder 1093)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204559 (Box 25, Folder 1094)
    - Molds. [perhaps of feathers], undated; 152692 (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_339f2f8de1b7cbb56ac1477b2cfd3e35)
    - Photo mat, undated; 152691 (Box 25, Folder 1095)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204560 (Box 25, Folder 1096)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204561 (Box 25, Folder 1097)
    - Sketch board, undated; 152690 (Box 25, Folder 1098)
    - small organisms. green ink on beige paper, undated; 152689 (Box 25, Folder 1099)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204562 (Box 25, Folder 1100)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204563 (Box 25, Folder 1101)
    - Stencils, pills, undated; 152688 (Box 25, Folder 1102)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous, 152675
    - Bee on a string, undated; 152686 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_edcf04c736ac377b8ff5ccf01652d4eb)
    - Beanie, purple, pink and white, undated; 152685 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_52c73a2102a852ce66de1422c1e8ac59)
    - Confederate States of America fifty dollar bill, 1864; 152684 (Box 25, Folder 1103)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204553 (Box 25, Folder 1104)
    - Mask, foam., undated; 152683 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_a723f6084563aae4b9ba8e578cfb6312)
    - Name tag from Academy Award in Art function., undated; 152682 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_d6ee725819e1887797a1ac84a4453a21)
    - Pins [possibly hat pins], undated; 152681 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_be81cede6bced6e808d277c5ae6cd5fc)
    - Pin. "Queer eyes, Queer-ize", undated; 152680 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_c2f32e0f9861af85f30f0c048cf7a898)
    - Pouch. Plastic, zebra striped, pink lettering "Savage", undated; 152679 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_34e8f35a71aca5eb0fac92d24d01a6bb)
    - Red ribbons. Used at "A Day Without Art" Original AIDS Ribbons, 1991; 152678 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_abd21ae3bd5be2d2d4b31c4342b93621)
    - Red Ribbon. Two large ribbons. "A Day Without AIDS" and "Work for a Cure", undated; 152677 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_769d24d20720aa579b4dd7e132fe3aa1)
    - T-shirt, design by Kenny Scharf. Drawing of Betty from the Flintstones., undated; 152676 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_d43f240296e5bb04ba8088ecd769e776)
- Series IX: Juvenalia and Family Memorabilia, 152659
  Series nine contains two subseries. Subseries A:Juvenalia, items relating to Frank Moore's life before his art career such as a year book and diploma. Subseries B: Family Memorabilia holds personal, family related information such as birth and death announcements.
  - Subseries A: Juvenalia, 152669
    - Broadside critiquing physical education program at Roslyn High School. Written by Richie Ruchman. Illustrated by Frank Moore., undated; 152673 (Box 25, Folder 1105)
    - Roslyn High School Yearbook, 1971; 152672 (Box 25, Folder 1106)
    - School correspondence regarding Frank Moore, 1962; 152671 (Box 25, Folder 1107)
    - Selective Service classification, 1972; 152670 (Box 25, Folder 1108)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204552 (Box 25, Folder 1109)
  - Subseries B: Family Memorabilia, 152660
    - Birth Announcement, Violet Moore Schneider, 1990; 152668 (Box 25, Folder 1110)
    - Burt, Arthur Hartwell. Frank Moore's maternal grandfather. Photograph of Arthur Burt, vice president of Sherwin-Williams paints in Cleveland, Ohio., undated; 152667 (Box 25, Folder 1111)
    - Dickinson, Blair. Memorial service program, 1984; 152666 (Box 25, Folder 1112)
    - Harris, John Rockwell. Materials regarding his memorial service. Harris was Frank Moore's stepbrother., 1990; 152665 (Box 25, Folder 1113)
    - Harris, Sarah Burt. Materials regarding her memorial service, she was Frank Moore's mother., 1997; 152664 (Box 25, Folder 1114)
    - Hodermarsky, Daniel. Memorial announcement. Hodermarsky was Frank Moore's uncle., 1999; 152663 (Box 25, Folder 1115)
    - Moore, Frank Charles. Frank Moore's paternal grandfather. Biography, Izaak Walton League address and Wherret Lecture publication. Frank C. Moore was Lieutenant Governor of New York., ca. 1951; 152662 (Box 25, Folder 1116)
    - Photographs, miscellaneous, undated; 152661 (Box 25, Folder 1117)
- Series X: Printed Materials, 152367
  This series contains printed materials from Frank Moore's library including books, newspapers, magazines and art catalogues. Materials are organized alphabetically by author last name where available or alphabetically by title.
  - Subseries A: Brochures, Merchandise Catalogues, and Owner's Manuals, 152648
    - Appliance Owner's Manuals, undated; 152658 (Box 25, Folder 1118)
    - Brushes for the Arts and Trades. General Catalogue. April 1956., 152657 (Box 25, Folder 1119)
    - Carroll Gardens Incorporated Plant Catalogue, 1994; 152656 (Box 25, Folder 1120)
    - French travel brochures, undated; 152655 (Box 25, Folder 1121)
    - Home Depot Professional Equipment and Supply Catalogue, 2000; 152654 (Box 25, Folder 1122)
    - Libidinous Modernity. Babes and Horny catalogue, undateed; 152653 (Box 25, Folder 1123)
    - Oil Colors, ca. 1998; 152652 (Box 25, Folder 1124)
    - Talas catalogue. Preservation, conservation and restoration supplies., undated; 152651 (Box 25, Folder 1125)
    - Tourist information: Italy, undated; 152650 (Box 25, Folder 1126)
    - Venini lighting, undated; 152649 (Box 25, Folder 1127)
  - Subseries B: Artist Catalogues, 152574
    - Abstract Painting: 1960-1969 at PS 1, ca. 1982; 152647 (Box 25, Folder 1128)
    - L'Art de la Poterie en France de Rodin a Dufy. Exhibit of the national ceramics museum. June-October 1971., 152646 (Box 25, Folder 1129)
    - The art of the Real USA 1948-1968. Museum of Modern Art, New York, undated; 152645 (Box 25, Folder 1130)
    - Art Treasures from the Vienna Collections 1949-1950, 152644 (Box 30, Folder 1131)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231780
    - Francis Bacon at the Museo d'Arte Moderna., 1993; 152643 (Box 30, Folder 1132)
    - Bakker, Gabrielle at Mincher/Wilcox Gallery, San Francisco, 1991; 152642 (Box 30, Folder 1133)
    - Balthus: paintings and Drawings 1934-1977 at Pierre Matisse Gallery., 152641 (Box 30, Folder 1134)
    - Vanessa Bell 1879-1961 at Davis and Long COmpany, New York, 1980; 152640 (Box 30, Folder 1135)
    - Beyond Loss: Art in the Era of AIDS., 1993; 152639 (Box 30, Folder 1136)
    - James Bishop. Galerie nationale du Jeu de Paume., 1993; 152638 (Box 30, Folder 1137)
    - Probert Blanchon at the Lost Angeles Center for Photographic Studies., 1996-1997; 152637 (Box 30, Folder 1138)
    - Nancy Bowen and Nancy Davidson.Figuring the BOdy. at the Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery., 1998; 152636 (Box 30, Folder 1139)
    - Gianni Burattoni, 1992; 152635 (Box 30, Folder 1140)
    - Giorgio de Chirico. Museum of Modern art. exhibit program cover., 1982; 152634 (Box 30, Folder 1141)
    - Christo and Jeanne-Claude: Early Works. Martin Gropius Bau, Berlin, 2001; 152633 (Box 30, Folder 1142)
    - Edgar Degas 1834-1917 at Wildenstein, NEw York, 1949; 152632 (Box 30, Folder 1143)
    - Charles Demuth Poster Portraits 1923-1929 at Yale University Art Gallery, New Haven., 1995; 152631 (Box 30, Folder 1144)
    - Derain. "Hommage a Derain" at La Galerie Paul Vallotton S.A., 1975; 152630 (Box 30, Folder 1145A)
    - A. Derain 1880-1954 at Galerie Schmit. May 12-June 20, 1976, 152629 (Box 30, Folder 1145B)
    - Andre Derain, 1880-1954. Paintings and Drawings at Theo Waddington and Co. Inc., New York., 1981; 152628 (Box 30, Folder 1146)
    - Andre Derain, 1880-1954. Watercolours, gouaches, mixed media from the period 1930-1953 at Victor Waddington, London., 1977; 152627 (Box 30, Folder 1147)
    - Raoul Dufy, ceramiques at Galerie LANDROT, Paris., 1990; 152626 (Box 30, Folder 1148)
    - Estrujenbank. March-April 1990., 152625 (Box 30, Folder 1149)
    - Expressive Heads at Jason McCoy Inc. New York May 6-June 12, 1993., 152624 (Box 30, Folder 1150)
    - Fantin-Latour: Flowers, Fruits, Figures at Scott and Fowles, New York. March 26-April 14, 1951, 152623 (Box 30, Folder 1151)
    - Futuruismo and Futurismi: oggetti futuristi [Futurist objects], 1986; 152622 (Box 30, Folder 1152)
    - Joy Garnett: Rocket Science at Debs and Co. New York., 2001; 152621 (Box 30, Folder 1153)
    - Alan Glass: 1971-1991 at Claude Bernard Gallery, New York., 152620 (Box 30, Folder 1154)
    - Gnoli, 1985; 152619 (Box 30, Folder 1155)
    - Stephen Hannock at James Graham and Sons, New York., 1996; 152618 (Box 30, Folder 1156)
    - Stephen Hannock: Space and Time at Charles P. Russell Gallery, Deerfield MA and Dayton Art Institute, Dayton Ohio., 1998-1999; 152617 (Box 30, Folder 1157)
    - Geoffrey Hendricks: Day into Night, 1993-1994; 152616 (Box 30, Folder 1158)
    - Florence Henri, 1976; 152615 (Box 30, Folder 1159)
    - Elana Herzog: The Carpet Prardigm at Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery, Wesleyan University., 1998; 152614 (Box 30, Folder 1160A)
    - David Hockney: New Paintings, Drawings and Graphics at Andre Emmerich Gallery, 1977; 152613 (Box 30, Folder 1160B)
    - James Hyde at John Good Gallery, New York., 1989; 152612 (Box 30, Folder 1161)
    - Win Knowlton at The Museum of Modern Art., 1986; 152611 (Box 30, Folder 1162)
    - Leo Lionni: il tavolo nero at Galleria Giulia, Rome and Galleria Eva Menzio, Torino. inscribed., 1992-1993; 152610 (Box 30, Folder 1163)
    - Leo Lionni: dipanit, sculture, disegni. at Galleria del Milione., 1972; 152609 (Box 30, Folder 1164)
    - Lazar el Lissitzky. Architectural Models: Lenin Tribune 1920/1924., 1984; 152608 (Box 30, Folder 1165)
    - Man Ray: Sotheby's auction catalog., 1995; 152607 (Box 30, Folder 1166)
    - John Marin Etchings 1905-1951 at Marlborough Fine Art, New York., 1971; 152606 (Box 30, Folder 1167)
    - Jean Mayodon Ceramiste at La Galerie Landrot, Paris, undated; 152605 (Box 30, Folder 1168)
    - Mental Illness Illustrated, Yale Medical Library New Haven., 1962; 152604 (Box 30, Folder 1169)
    - la Metafora Travata at Galleria Sperone, Rome., 1994; 152603 (Box 30, Folder 1170)
    - Joan Mitchell at the Whitney Museum of American Art, 1974; 152602 (Box 30, Folder 1171)
    - Giorgio Morandi Retrospective 1912-1957 at World House Galleries., 152601 (Box 30, Folder 1172)
    - Moti at Debs and Co., 2000; 152600 (Box 30, Folder 1173)
    - Nabil Nahas at Sperone Westwater, New York., undated; 152599 (Box 30, Folder 1174)
    - New York School: The First Generation at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1965; 152598 (Box 31, Folder 1175)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231798
    - The Norman Fisher Collection at the Jacksonville Art Museum, 1980; 152597 (Box 31, Folder 1176)
    - Oskar Schlemmer: Das Triadische Ballett., 1980; 152596 (Box 31, Folder 1177)
    - Christian Peltenburg-Brechneff: Mountain and Sea. inscribed, 1997; 152595 (Box 31, Folder 1178)
    - Filippo de Pisis at Galleria Philippe Daverio., 1980; 152594 (Box 31, Folder 1179)
    - de Pisis, 1983; 152593 (Box 31, Folder 1180)
    - Filippo de Pisis at Galleriea Gian Ferrari, Arte Moderna., 1994; 152592 (Box 31, Folder 1181)
    - Photographs: Sotheby's auction., 1983; 152591 (Box 31, Folder 1182)
    - Donald Richie: Nudes., 1997; 152590 (Box 31, Folder 1183)
    - Alberto Saviinino: Musician, Writer and Painter at Paolo Baldacci Gallery, 1995; 152589 (Box 31, Folder 1184)
    - The Seascpae: Avery and the European Masters at Borgenicht Gallery New York., 1976; 152588 (Box 31, Folder 1185)
    - Beverly Semmes: Not Here at the Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery, 1999; 152587 (Box 31, Folder 1187)
    - Dean Smith: Drawings at Christopher Grimes Gallery, 2001; 152586 (Box 31, Folder 1188)
    - Soutine at Gallerie Yoshii, 1974; 152585 (Box 31, Folder 1189)
    - Speedy Graphito: Dou venons-nous?, 1991; 152584 (Box 31, Folder 1190)
    - Southerland: Bees., 1977; 152583 (Box 31, Folder 1191)
    - Ten Americans: masters of Watercolor at Andrew Crispo Gallery, New York., 1974; 152582 (Box 31, Folder 1192)
    - Fred Tomaselli at James Cohan Gallery, New York. Inscribed, 2000; 152581 (Box 31, Folder 1193)
    - Transcend AIDS: Work by Los Angeles Artists with HIV/AIDS., 1995; 152580 (Box 31, Folder 1194)
    - Cy Twombly: Paintings and Draawings at the Milwaukee Art Center., 1968; 152579 (Box 31, Folder 1195)
    - Uprising: Videotapes on the Palestinain Resistance, undated; 152578 (Box 31, Folder 1196)
    - The Collection of Gianni Versace: Sotheby's Auction Catalogue., 2001; 152577 (Box 31, Folder 1197)
    - Vorticism and its Allies, 1974; 152576 (Box 31, Folder 1198)
    - Andrew Wyeth. organized by Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts at the Whitney Museum of American Art, New York., 1967; 152575 (Box 31, Folder 1199)
  - Subseries C: Periodicals, 152548
    - AIDS Treatment News #190, undated; 152573 (Box 31, Folder 1200)
    - AIDS Treatment News #197 April 15, 1994, 152572 (Box 31, Folder 1201)
    - American Art and Antiques, november-December 1978, 152571 (Box 31, Folder 1202)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research. Summer 1990 Report., 152570 (Box 31, Folder 1203)
    - Art Forum, April 1996, 152569 (Box 31, Folder 1204)
    - The Arts. February 1931., 152568 (Box 31, Folder 1205)
    - C: International contemporary Art. issue number 62, May-August 1999, 152567 (Box 31, Folder 1206)
    - Casper the Friendly Ghost. Comic. August 1982, #223, 152566 (Box 31, Folder 1207)
    - Christopher Street., 1978; 152565 (Box 31, Folder 1208)
    - Digraphe #62, June 1993, 152564 (Box 31, Folder 1209)
    - Gai havdo Pied #124, 1984; 152563 (Box 31, Folder 1211)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis Newsletter. 8:2 (March 1994), 152562 (Box 31, Folder 1212)
    - Glass #46 (Winter 1991-1992), 152561 (Box 31, Folder 1213)
    - Innovations [lettering artists], 1986; 152560 (Box 31, Folder 1214)
    - Iranian Institute Bulletin 5:4, Mural Paintings from the Cave Temples of India., 1942; 152559 (Box 31, Folder 1215)
    - Th Lambda Update 10:2 (Winter 1992), 1993; 152558 (Box 31, Folder 1216)
    - New York Times Magazine (10 November 1996), 152557 (Box 31, Folder 1220)
    - The Poetry Project volume 155 (December/January 1994-1995), 152556 (Box 31, Folder 1221)
    - School of Visual Arts Almuni Magazine. Illustration issue. Winter 2002., 152555 (Box 30, Folder 1222)
    - The Sewanee Reveiw 87:4 (Fall 1979), 152554 (Box 31, Folder 1223)
    - Shiney International (Spring 1986), 152553 (Box 31, Folder 1224)
    - Soceity of Scribes, LTD. Journal. 1:3, 1989; 152552 (Box 31, Folder 1225)
    - TAG Line [Treatment Action Group] 8:6 (July-August 2001), 152551 (Box 31, Folder 1226)
    - Tricycle: The Buddist Review (Spring 1992), 152550 (Box 31, Folder 1227)
    - White Crane: Journal for the exploration of gay men's spirituality. #16, 1993; 152549 (Box 31, Folder 1228)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous, 152541
    - Air France Concorde Menu, undated; 152547 (Box 31, Folder 1234)
    - America Fashion Awards at Avery Fisher, Thursday June 15, 2000, 152546 (Box 31, Folder 1234A)
    - Inflight Movie Program: The Silent One, undated; 152545 (Box 31, Folder 1237)
    - Kiss the Children Goodbye: The Real Meaning of Nuclear War. A project of Women Strike for Peace., undated; 152544 (Box 31, Folder 1238)
    - MAC gift certificate for fifty dollars, undated; 152543 (Box 31, Folder 1239)
    - Menu for Chanterelle for January 22- February 17 1996, with printed cyanotype on cover by John Dugdale, 152542 (Box 31, Folder 1240)
  - Subseries E: Books, 152368
    - Afghan Trucks, 1976; 152540 (Box 32, Folder 1244)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231806
    - AIDS Treatment News Vol. 2 edited by John S. James, Denny Smith, Michelle Roland, and Laura Thomas., 1989-1991; 152539 (Box 32, Folder 1245)
    - AIDS Treatment News Vol. 3 edited by John S. James, 1991-1993; 152538 (Box 32, Folder 1246)
    - Alloway, Lawrence American Pop Art, 1974; 152537 (Box 32, Folder 1248)
    - Ashbery, John and Thomas B. Hess. Painterly Painting, 1971; 152536 (Box 32, Folder 1249)
    - Awakawa, Yasuichi Zen Painting, 1982; 152535 (Box 32, Folder 1251)
    - Ballard, Ernest Days in My Garden, 1919; 152534 (Box 32, Folder 1252)
    - Barlow, T.D. Woodcuts of Albrecht Durer, 1948; 152533 (Box 32, Folder 1253)
    - Baudelaire, Charles Les Fleurs du Mal, 1972; 152532 (Box 32, Folder 1254)
    - Beary, Kevin. Florentine Locutions: a study of blasphemous and obscene expressions in Florentine Italian, 1992; 152531 (Box 32, Folder 1255)
    - Benjamin, Walter Charles Baudelaire: A Lyric Poet in the Era of High Capitalism, 1976; 152530 (Box 32, Folder 1256)
    - Bergson, Henri Creative Evolution, 1944; 152529 (Box 32, Folder 1257)
    - Between Street and Mirror: The Drawings of James Ensor, 2001; 152528 (Box 32, Folder 1258)
    - Joseph Beuys: Heiner Stachelhaus translated by David Britt, 1987; 152527 (Box 32, Folder 1259)
    - The Biophilia Hypothesis Edited by Stephen R. Kellert and Edward O. Wilson, 1993; 152526 (Box 32, Folder 1260)
    - Bible Revised Standared Version, 1952; 152525 (Box 33, Folder 1261)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231814
    - Blair, Les Jest Tawk: a country dictionary spiced with country sayins., 1986; 152524 (Box 33, Folder 1262)
    - Bosman, Richard and Ted Greenwald Exit the Face, 1982; 152523 (Box 33, Folder 1263)
    - Boswell, John Christianity, Social Tolerance and Homosexuality. Drawing in back cover, 1980; 152522 (Box 33, Folder 1264)
    - Brambila, Rosa Sala de Teotihuacan, 1989; 152521 (Box 33, Folder 1265)
    - Buber, Martin I and Thou, 1958; 152520 (Box 33, Folder 1267)
    - Burchfield, Charles The Charles Rand Penney Collection of Works., 1995; 152519 (Box 33, Folder 1268)
    - Burke, Edmund Reflections on the Revolution in France, 1955; 152518 (Box 33, Folder 1269)
    - Callaway, C. Wayne and Catherine Whitney Surviving with AIDS, 1991; 152517 (Box 33, Folder 1270)
    - Caractere Noel, undated; 152516 (Box 33, Folder 1271)
    - Carli, Enzo The Maesta duccio de Buoninsegna, undated; 152515 (Box 33, Folder 1272)
    - Carlisle, Lilian Baker Hat Boxes and Dandboxes at Shelburne Museum, 1960; 152514 (Box 33, Folder 1273)
    - Cassirer, Ernst The Philosophy of the Enlightenment, 1951; 152513 (Box 33, Folder 1274)
    - Carnegie, Dale How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1937; 152512 (Box 33, Folder 1275)
    - Catullo, Luciano The Ancient Roman Villa of Casale at Piazza Armerina: Past and Present, 1999; 152511 (Box 33, Folder 1276)
    - Charbonnel Encres D'Imprimerie, undated; 152510 (Box 33, Folder 1277)
    - Coleridge, 1959; 152509 (Box 33, Folder 1278)
    - CONASIDA Preguntas y Respuestas sobre SIDA del Personal de Salud, 1991; 152508 (Box 33, Folder 1279)
    - Cunault, 1964; 152507 (Box 33, Folder 1280)
    - Debreczeny, Paul Alexander Pushkin: Complete Prose Fiction., 1983; 152506 (Box 34, Folder 1284)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231822
    - Deitcher, David Dear Friends: American Photographs of Men Together 1840-1918. annotated, 2001; 152505 (Box 34, Folder 1285)
    - Delevoy, Robert Bosch, 1990; 152504 (Box 34, Folder 1286)
    - Diaz-Bolio, Jose The Geometry of the Maya and their Rattlesnake Art, 1965; 152503 (Box 34, Folder 1287)
    - Diego Rivera y la Salud, 1986; 152502 (Box 34, Folder 1289)
    - Easton, Robert and Peter Nabokov Native American Architecture, 1989; 152501 (Box 34, Folder 1290)
    - Ehrenzweig, Anton The Hidden Order of Art. with annotations, 1971; 152500 (Box 34, Folder 1291)
    - Eliade, Mircea Cosmos and History: The Myth of the Eternal Return, 1959; 152499 (Box 34, Folder 1292)
    - Eliade, Mircea The Sacred and the Profane: The Nature of Religion., 1961; 152498 (Box 34, Folder 1293)
    - Eliot, T.S. Four Quartets., 1971; 152497 (Box 34, Folder 1294)
    - Eliot, T.S. The Waste Land and other Poems, 1962; 152496 (Box 34, Folder 1295)
    - Ellsworth Kelly, 1973; 152495 (Box 34, Folder 1296)
    - Erdman, David V. The Poetry and Prose of William Blake., 1970; 152494 (Box 34, Folder 1297)
    - Erlande-Brandenburg, Aiain La Dame a la Licorne, 1978; 152493 (Box 34, Folder 1298)
    - Ernst, Max Une Semaine de Bonte, 1976; 152492 (Box 34, Folder 1299)
    - Feininger, Lyonel The Ruin by the Sea, 1968; 152491 (Box 34, Folder 1300)
    - Ficke, Arthur Davison Chats on Japanese Prints, 1928; 152490 (Box 34, Folder 1301)
    - Field, Eugene The Tribune Primer, 1900; 152489 (Box 34, Folder 1302)
    - Fifty Years of Modern Art, 1959; 152488 (Box 35, Folder 1303)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231830
    - Foucault, Michele The Care of the Self: The History of Sexuality vol. 3, 1988; 152487 (Box 35, Folder 1304)
    - Frazer, James George The Golden Bough, 1937; 152486 (Box 35, Folder 1305)
    - Friedman, Michael Special Capacity, 1992; 152485 (Box 35, Folder 1306)
    - Gallery of Masterpieces: Mona Lisa Gallery of Masterpieces: The Massacre of Chios, 1947; 152484 (Box 35, Folder 1307)
    - Gian Enzo Sperone, undated; 152483 (Box 35, Folder 1308)
    - Gluck, Robert Jack the Modernist, 1985; 152482 (Box 35, Folder 1309)
    - Glucksmann, Andre La felure du monde, 1994; 152481 (Box 35, Folder 1310)
    - Greenly, Mike Chronicle: The Human Side of AIDS, 1986; 152480 (Box 35, Folder 1312)
    - Greenwald, Ted Common Sense with annotations, 1978; 152479 (Box 35, Folder 1313)
    - Grimes, Nancy Jared French's Myths, 1993; 152478 (Box 35, Folder 1314)
    - Guide Indicateur des Reus de Paris, undated; 152477 (Box 35, Folder 1315)
    - Hastreiter, Laurie A photo- typo-graphic essay on water., 1976; 152476 (Box 35, Folder 1316)
    - Herodotus The Struggle for Greece, 1962; 152475 (Box 35, Folder 1317)
    - Hess, Thomas Willem de Kooning, 1968; 152474 (Box 35, Folder 1318)
    - Hibbert, Christopher The Emperors of China, 1981; 152473 (Box 35, Folder 1319)
    - Hockney, David Secret Knowledge with annotations, 2001; 152472 (Box 36, Folder 1320)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231848
    - Hockney, David Six Fair Tales, 1970; 152471 (Box 36, Folder 1321)
    - Houellebecq, Michel Les particules elementaires, 1998; 152470 (Box 36, Folder 1322)
    - Houghton, Norris Great Russian Short Stories, 1960; 152469 (Box 36, Folder 1323)
    - Hunter, Sam Modern America Op, Pop and the School of Color, 1970; 152468 (Box 36, Folder 1324)
    - Huyghe, Rene The Contemporaries, 1940; 152467 (Box 36, Folder 1325)
    - Imuthiol in HIV Infection, 1989; 152466 (Box 36, Folder 1326)